Oh, man, my delts
are blasted.
I wish they had
a chart for how much
protein powder to scoop
for a 180-pound
man with no fat.
Protein powder, huh?
You cut it with water?
Why don't you
just take estrogen?
Here.
(COUGHING)
There you go, boys.
See how Papa
takes care of you.
(LAUGHS)
I remember when
people thought biceps
were all that.
They'd flex them all
night at the discotheque.
I bet you think it's
all about core, huh?
Yeah.
Core's critical.
There are four tenets
of Pilates that I
live my life by.
One, lengthen.
Two, elongate.
Listen, guys.
I think we all want to
know the same thing, right?
Who's the strongest?
There's only one
way to solve that.
Thigh curl contest.
All right,
here we go, everybody.
May the manliest man win.
Go!
(GRUNTING)
DWIGHT: Feast on this, Lewis!
I love the burn.
The burn is where I live.
Come on, Gabe.
You can't handle
his hamstrings.
You're getting hypno-thized.
GABE: Speed set. One...
One, two...
Here, this is for your elbows.
For your elbows.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Five, six...
MEREDITH: Seven.
Quick phone call for you guys.
Keep going. Eight.
ALL: Nine.
Hello?
ALL: Ten.
JIM: We got it?
Very funny, Jim.
Yeah, Jim.
Way to mock us for
perfecting our bodies.
Everyone, conference room.
Now.
(GROANS)
All right.
Easy there, Grandpa.
I don't need your help.
Okay, you don't
need my help?
Here, here, just...
Morning.
Hey.
Somebody left in such
a hurry this morning
that she forgot
these.
Oh.
You know, the only thing
more delicious than
your feet
is the feast that I am going
to prepare for everyone.
Andy,
if you're going to
hang out for a while...
Uh...
What's this?
This dumb,
new rule Robert made.
He just wants
visitors to sign in.
Is this Robert's
attempt to embarrass me?
No, of course not.
It's just... I think it's
like if we make
an exception for you,
then we have to make an
exception for the water guy,
and then it's like,
"Where does it end?"
So, just...
ANDY: Why is it when other
people spend all their time
at the office,
they're rewarded for it,
and when I do it,
I am told,
"It's a little much"?
Is it because I'm not
an employee anymore?
Because that's
what it feels like.
All right,
enjoy the Illinois game.
Good, we have a deal?
Thanks, Janet.
Thanks so much, Earl.
Wow. A simultaneous sale.
And they said it
couldn't be done. Boom.
Screw them.
A lot going on, guys.
What's happening?
The Binghamton
branch closed last night,
and all their
clients are up for grabs.
That was a fine branch.
Things are really bad
under Robert California,
I guess.
It's like a festival of poo.
Hey, come on, language.
Yeah, and we're not
interested in your
sour grapes, okay?
Jim, tell him where he
can stick his grapes.
In the fridge.
No, Jim.
The butt, in his butt.
Sorry, man,
I can't focus on zingers.
There's too many
potential clients.
You two better
watch yourselves.
Yeah, the Syracuse
branch can't be happy
you're taking
New York clients.
(SHUSHING)
(RETCHING)
Robert, why did
Binghamton close?
Can everyone just...
Please.
I had a one-man
saturnalia last night
in celebration of
the finalization
of my divorce.
I got into a case
of Australian reds,
and, how should I say this,
Colombian whites.
Wait, what is this
about Binghamton?
The branch closed, forever.
Closing the Binghamton branch
never occurred to
me before today.
Or, I guess, last night.
But, in vino veritas,
as they say.
I'm not going to start
doubting my drunken self now.
I got your voice
mail from last night.
Wonderful.
And the answer is yes,
yes, yes, yes,
and never.
Pam, when's the last time
you lived so intensely
that your brain, literally,
couldn't hold the memories in?
It was the summer...
Apparently,
I left a phone message
for Nellie last night,
and I need you to
find out what I said.
Um, I am a little busy.
Yes.
Of course.
Why don't you list the things
that would keep
you from helping me?
Yeah. I can make you a list.
Let's do it now.
What's number one?
Why don't I help you now?
Okay.
There we go.
Who the hell are Jim Halpert
and Dwight Schrute?
Jim, Dwight,
what are your last names?
And you are?
Harry Jannerone,
Dunder Mifflin Syracuse.
What the hell's all this?
Cherries jubilee
over home-made gelato.
You live well down here in PA.
I want to talk to
you guys right now.
And Lloyd Gross, too.
Which one's that guy?
The salesmen have
a commission cap,
but we figured
out a way around it.
Lloyd Gross is a fictional
salesman we invented to...
How do I put this?
Steal from the company,
embezzle, to commit fraud.
Okay, it sounds sketchy,
but it helps us
get more money.
Yes.
Pam made a drawing
of Lloyd.
He is a blend of
all the salesmen.
There he is.
That's Lloyd.
Me?
Yeah, you.
Where do you get off
crossing state lines?
Now, we're actually closer to
Binghamton than you are,
kemo sabe.
I like to think Lloyd Gross
is a no-nonsense guy
who doesn't back
down from anybody,
and he calls
people "kemo sabe."
They're New York,
we're New York.
State line is
the dividing line.
That's the way
it's always been.
There's actually not
a rule that says that.
It's true.
It's true. There's no rule.
You can check
the employee handbook.
Can I check
the employee handbook, Lloyd?
Does it say anything about
me choking a man
with my bare hands?
No.
Wait, no? Are you kidding me?
You told me there was a rule.
I could have choked
so many people by now.
Stay out of my state.
It's in your best interest
to stay out of my state.
I've seen guys
like you, big guys
who like to push
the little guys around.
Lloyd Gross eats bullies
like you for breakfast.
Stay out of New York, Lloyd!
Text from the old wife.
I'm going to take that.
How about this,
why don't we just
ask Robert?
Can we all agree
that maybe the CEO
should decide this?
Robert's here?
Look at us,
bickering like school girls,
looking around
the room for things
to hit each other with.
I don't think we
were doing that.
Chair, lamp,
plant, table leg,
Jim's leg.
Where's the Advil, Jim?
I think I've hit my
limit on the Tylenol...
Sorry, not Jim.
Andrew, what do we
have to do to
get rid of you?
Hire you back and send
Erin back to Florida?
Message received
loud and clear.
Just have to get
the caramelized sugar
off the pan
before it dries.
Oh, for God's sake...
Robert California,
what a surprise
you're here in Scranton.
Harry.
So, why would you
close Binghamton down
without a transition plan
in place?
How do you mean?
I forgot...
No, no, no, kid, stay there.
Do your dishes. Go ahead.
Harry, there is a time
for every decision
predetermined
many years ago.
There's no benefit
in questioning why
this particular
decision seems
so poorly timed.
Okay, what are you deciding?
We get a say.
Listen,
Robert, I don't have time.
There's a big client in play,
Prestige Direct Mail Solutions
used to be Binghamton's...
Don't listen to him.
Nope.
I want it. It's mine.
Prestige is ours.
Okay, they're responsible
for half of the junk mail
on the eastern seaboard.
We get them.
We already put
a call in to them, Robert.
We need you to
make a decision.
Make a decision.
I have decided.
Neither of you are
to have any contact
with either Prestige
or any other Binghamton client
until I've figured out
how to divide things up.
As Solomon once said...
There's some bizarre energy
in this place today.
Robert going off the rails,
making some funky decisions.
Like why is nobody
going to call on Prestige?
That is a huge client.
They could give
their business to
the first person to
walk in the door.
Could be any idiot.
Any idiot at all.
Shaping a company is,
in a sense, similar
to training a geisha.
You have to mold
not merely the physical form,
but also the character.
The two must harmonize.
Are they still there?
They want a decision,
who gets the big client.
They can wait.
I'll still be talking
about geishas
long past their bedtime.
You know, I trained as one.
Is it just me,
or is our boss a
freaking weirdo?
I'm going to get some air.
Jim, you know what would
be really dastardly?
If we snuck out of here
and got to the client first.
(CHUCKLES)
He's running!
Damn it!
Damn it.
What...
What is this
supposed to be?
It's a monkey.
Jim, get real.
This is not a monkey.
It's got a hula skirt
and a blue nose.
Hold on. Hold on.
Is this him?
What?
Is that him?
It's him!
Do something!
Get out! Go!
JIM: What? What am I
going to do? I don't...
Go slash his tires!
Go dent his hood!
DWIGHT: That's it?
That's great.
That's like a 5-second delay.
JIM: Dwight!
DWIGHT: Go!
Does this thing have turbo?
Nitrous? Hit the NOS.
NOS? You mean like
in Fast & Furious?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah,
I definitely have NOS.
Hit the NOS.
Are you sure?
Yes. We got it! Go!
Brace yourself.
Three, two, one.
Here we go!
Hello.
Andy Bernard
to see the CEO.
Oh. Do you have
an appointment?
No, I do not.
Okay. I think I can
squeeze you in.
Seriously?
Because I could just
be anyone. I thought
I was going to
have to convince you.
He's really not that busy.
Is there someone
here to see me?
Yes. This man.
Come on in.
So, what do
you make of this
Robert California guy?
What does a guy
like that do on an
average weeknight.
I'll tell you what he does.
Hello.
Hello, my clucking hens.
Got room for
another in the roost?
Huh? Don't worry.
I won't lay an egg.
Robert sent me to
take over if Pam fails.
If?
(LAUGHING)
I have been
crunching numbers all day.
Math is for boys.
I need girl talk.
Did someone say "girl talk?"
Sometimes I wonder
if I have ovaries
in my scrotum
because I am
great at girl talk.
Have you guys been
watching any good
Korean soap operas?
I'm pretty deep into
Hee-Jung Cinderella Girl.
Although, I definitely
fast-forward through
the Yung Tae storylines.
Do you think I'd like that?
Or is it important to
have an Asian fetish?
I think you're going to need
to have an Asian fetish. Yeah.
It'll be
upsetting if you don't.
I'm a former paper executive.
I know the product.
I know the margins.
I can save you
25% on your costs.
Why haven't I heard of you?
You got any references?
No. I'm a rogue.
Uh-huh.
Which is the best part.
That means you will
be my first customer,
and your
business will get 100%
of my attention.
Now, I have written down
my personal phone number.
You call this any time.
Every salesman I've ever met
has given me his
personal phone number.
Of course they have,
which is why I'm giving you
a key to my house.
Whatever you need, any time,
night or day,
you just stop on by.
You want me to
drive to your house
if I need paper?
Maybe you just want
someone to talk to,
maybe you need
a place to crash
for a couple of days.
My wireless password
is "eat, pray, love."
Easy to remember.
Ready? Go, go, go!
(YELLING)
You all right?
Yeah.
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
Dwight, what are you doing?
Shh.
Go! Go! Take the stairs, now!
What are you talking about?
Just run! Take the stairs!
I don't even know
where the stairs are.
DWIGHT: I'll stall him. Go!
What are you doing?
I'm going to activate
the seismic fail-safe.
We'll be stuck
between floors for hours.
Oh!
My pants fell down.
What?
My pants fell down!
I don't have a belt!
Hello, sir, good day.
Dwight K. Schrute,
Dunder Mifflin Scranton.
Forgive my pants,
they fell down.
An appointment with
Mr. Ramish, please.
Right now is fine.
No, no, no. I was here first.
Dwight K. Schrute,
Dunder Mifflin Scranton.
Hi, guys. What's going on?
Mr. Ramish, Harry Jannerone,
Dunder Mifflin Syracuse.
I was here first.
Sorry about this mix-up.
Okay.
I already made
an appointment with
your secretary.
Let me stop you
all right here.
I've already picked
a new paper supplier.
Wait, it's not
DM Utica, is it?
No, no, it's not Dunder
Mifflin at all, actually.
It's Big Red Paper Company.
Big Red Paper Company?
Mmm-hmm.
Yes, yes, yes!
Get me a cup of coffee.
Me too.
Or do you also have
a monopoly on thirst?
All right, guys,
it didn't work out
for any of us,
so we're still
on the same team.
Let me get these.
No.
Let him get his own.
He's got Syracuse money.
You know your partner's
got a lot of attitude,
but I like that.
How long you guys
been dating?
Jim couldn't land me
in a thousand years.
But you're saying
there's a chance.
Shut up.
Hey.
I stole Nellie's phone.
Excellent. Excellent.
Though troubling
that your first instinct
is thievery.
What do you want from me?
Now we get to the bottom
of Nellie's,
"Yes, yes, yes, yes, never."
Hello, Nell, it's Mum.
Do keep your chin up.
It can't possibly be
as bad as you describe.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, yes, it can.
MAN: This is MasterCard.
You are over the limit.
Send the minimum
payment of $448
by Monday,
or we will be forced to
send it to collections.
Shopaholic.
Sounds like it.
Yeah.
Hi, sis. Is your boss
still hitting on you?
WOMAN: This is Annie
from Second Nests.
I'm sorry, but
the Romanian orphanage
felt more comfortable
with a two-person
nuclear family
than a single mother,
so we're going to
hold out for that.
Okay, that's enough.
No, no, no.
Pam, we need to get
to the bottom of this.
No. No.
Come on. Come on.
Robert, okay...
So, I deleted them all.
They're all deleted.
Pam, you've
completely bungled this.
Ah...
Hey.
Can I do it, Pam?
Can I pull off
a gold Arabian sandal?
Um...
Yes. Definitely.
With your hair, certainly.
You dropped
your cell phone.
Oh, gosh.
Yep.
Thank you. I'm so stupid.
No. My goodness,
you just...
You have a lot going on
with Robert and everything.
Oh, God,
Pam, don't get me started.
No, I will not.
You've just got me started.
Robert is a filthy beast.
Don't you get
the feeling every time
he looks at you,
he's just thinking
of 15 different ways
to do you?
Well...
The man talks of
nothing but sex.
Sometimes he talks about
flesh and bacchanals.
Oh, yeah.
I cannot even tell you
what he left on my
phone last night.
No. Don't.
Just put it out
of your mind.
Pam, what is your address?
I'm going to
send you a pair of
these gold harem shoes.
Oh. No, you don't...
Yes.
Come on, a little
gold Arabian slipper.
Things are looking up.
I might be a mother soon.
I have MasterCard
right where I want them,
and I have a new friend.
A friend.
At work.
Erin.
There's a call
for you on line 1.
Who is it?
He says, "Salvation."
No last name.
Yeah, hello.
You once put me
on a list of the
losers in the office.
This loser just got
your biggest client
to give him all
their business.
So, hire me back,
that business is yours.
Don't, and I will
find another buyer.
You're blackmailing me.
It's just business.
I will not be blackmailed by
some ineffectual, privileged,
effete, soft-penised debutant.
You want to start
a street fight with me,
bring it on,
but you're going
to be surprised
by how ugly it gets.
You don't even
know my real name.
I'm the (BLEEP) Lizard King.
Whoa.
Well, I gave him a chance.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Andy Bernard?
You got a minute?
I'm in the middle
of a piano lesson.
I wanted to see
if could interest
you in an investment,
Dunder Mifflin.
Now, why would I want that?
It's worth half what
it was three years ago.
Exactly.
And you know better
than anyone that
with the right management,
it could be worth twice
what you would
pay for it today.
Why don't you come in?
So, what would you do if you
weren't selling paper?
Oh, man,
I'd have to sell beets,
probably submit
them for competition.
What?
Yeah, I know it
sounds stupid,
but nationals has
always kind of been
a dream of mine.
How have we never
talked about this before?
Wait, you don't even
care about nationals.
Nothing?
I don't know.
I've always wanted to
own a bike shop, but...
What about you?
I'd like to sell one
big thing, you know?
Like a plane.
One sale. I'm out.
That sounds lovely.
Anyway,
Robert's going to run this
company into the ground,
so we won't be doing
this in six months.